Answer the man, scum.
What do you want to do?
I want to join the Recon Corps,
and kill as many Titans as I can, sir!
Oh? Not bad.
Erwin. I'll take responsibility for him.
Tell that to the higher-ups.
Don't get me wrong. It's not like I trust him.
If he betrays us or goes berserk,
I'll put him down without hesitation.
Upstairs shouldn't have a problem with that...
Nobody except me is suited for the job.
I'll accept your application
to the Recon Corps.
♪ Look, my friend! ♪
♪ Now we have a real victory here ♪
♪ This is our first honor ♪
♪ Now, my friend, ♪
♪ let's celebrate this victory ♪
♪ to prepare for our next battle ♪
♪ No death will be in vain ♪
♪ Our battle will go on until ♪
♪ only a single arrow remains ♪
♪ Our foe is barbaric... But we'll get him... ♪
♪ Our foe is colossal... So we'll jump to him... ♪
♪ We wield honor in our arms ♪
♪ and sing in the name of victory ♪
♪ We bear the wings of freedom on our backs ♪
♪ Swearing upon our hearts, ♪
♪ we strike at the ring of madness ♪
♪ and soar through the sky ♪
♪ with our wings we call freedom ♪
Sync and corrections by masaca
- addic7ed.com -
Can't Look Into His Eyes- Prelude
to the Counterattack (pt 1)
Hey, is it true?
Are there really Titans that sided with us?
Come on, it's obviously just a rumor.
The retake campaign might've
failed, meaning lots
of people from Wall Rose
could be evacuating here.
Inside Wall Sina
But then we're bound to have
another food shortage...
What if the Titan that sided with
humans joins up with the Rose refugees,
and they attack us together?
Wall Rose
Wall Sina
This is huge news! A Titan has sided with us!
Inside Wall Rose
We might even be able to retake Wall Maria!
Say it!
Say it! He's our savior!
Savior, huh?
The common folk are always so irresponsible.
They might even try to using him to incite
rebellion against the Inner District.
As the Police, we must dispose of
Eren Jaeger before that can happen.
We won't let those freaks at the
Recon Corps get their hands on him.
Attention!
Salute the Supreme Commander!
It's hot.
Commander Pixis,
some people consider it inappropriate
for you, as Commander of the Garrison,
to be conversing privately with
someone like me from the Recon Corps.
Hm, you're as stiff as they say.
We merely ran into each other by
chance during our morning walks.
Now that we're already walking,
we might as well chat.
Have you heard that the Police
are also after Eren Jaeger?
Yes. They sent word yesterday.
A trial will be held.
The decision about whether the
Police or the Recon Corps get Eren
has been entrusted to Zacklay.
Zacklay?
Do you mean Supreme Commander Dallis Zacklay?
He's the man in charge
of all three forces: the
Military Police, the Garrison,
and the Recon Corps.
When making decisions, he
considers only one method:
the cost-benefit analysis.
That is, whether it's profitable
or harmful to mankind overall.
Which means he wouldn't hesitate
to execute Eren right on the spot,
if that were the verdict.
I don't want to let him kill Eren.
But unfortunately, more than a few
in my Garrison fear Eren's powers.
All I can do is to argue my
case against the Police.
Do you think you can win?
Yes.
I have also prepared a proposition,
but its viability depends greatly
on the way the trial progresses.
So you're planning to go in cold?
We of the Recon Corps are used to getting
chills from our work outside the Walls.
You aren't as stiff as you seem.
Thank you for such a nice
stroll, Colonel Smith.
Eren's being put on trial? For what?
I don't know the details.
I think it's about deciding
how to deal with Eren.
What does that mean?
They're probably deciding
whether he lives or dies.
Mikasa Ackerman! Armin Arlert!
Are you here?
Yes, sir!
You have been ordered to appear at the
trial this afternoon as witnesses!
Excuse me. May I use the toilet?
You just went earlier.
Can I get some water?
Hey! Understand the situation you're in.
Damn monster.
Monster? I guess they're not wrong about that.
Am I so scary that they need
to restrain me this much?
I shouldn't be that surprised. I don't
really understand all this myself.
I should just be happy that
I haven't been killed yet.
Wait a minute.
Those two weren't scared of me at all.
What are they doing now?
What happened to everybody else?
Be patient for a little longer.
We'll try to sort things out.
How many days have passed since then?
What's going on outside?
I won't have to live my whole
life like this, right?
So you're Eren, huh?
You okay? Feeling filthy?
Sorry for making you wait for so long.
You can finally leave this place.
Though you'll have to wear these.
I'm from the Recon Corps. Major Hanji Zoe.
He's fellow Major Mike Zacharias.
Um...
Ah, he just has this habit
of sniffing people at
their first meeting,
then laughing like that.
I wouldn't read much into it though.
He's skilled enough to
become a major, after all.
Oh, we chatted all the time away.
We're already here.
Well, I guess you're better off
without an explanation too.
We don't have a choice
but to trust you blindly.
Good luck.
A courtroom?
So I was being held under the courthouse?
Move along!
Currently Disclosable
Information:
Special court-martial (pt 1): A court for
judging those of military affiliation.
The judge, the prosecution, and
the defense are all soldiers too.
Currently Disclosable
Information:
Special court-martial (2): This proceeding has a lot
more political undertones than normal court-martials.
The final decision is handed down by the head of the
three forces, Supreme Commander Dallis Zacklay.
Kneel down there.
Why are these people here?
What is this trial even about?
Guys!
Now then, let us begin.
You are Eren Jaeger, right?
You're a soldier who vowed to
devote his life to the King.
Is that correct?
Yes, sir.
This is an exceptional case.
It is outside the
bounds of common law,
therefore we must convene
a special court-martial.
The final decision will be handed down by me.
We will deliberate upon whether
you live or die as well.
I knew it.
Do you have any objections?
None, sir.
I'm glad you're so cooperative.
Let me say this straightforwardly.
Concealing your existence
has proven impossible.
Unless we publicize your
existence in some way,
we will have to face another
threat besides the Titans.
This court is tasked with deciding
which force will take custody of you,
the Military Police or the Recon Corps.
First, let us hear the
proposition from the Police.
I am Nile Dawk, Chief of the Military Police.
Our proposition is as follows:
We will examine Eren's body thoroughly,
then dispose of him as soon as possible.
It's a fact that his Titan power
repelled the last attack.
However, his character induces disturbances
that may even lead to a rebellion.
Therefore he shall provide us with
as much intelligence as possible,
then he'll become a martyr for mankind.
That isn't necessary.
He's a vermin that breached and
infiltrated the sacred Walls of God.
He's from the Church of the Walls.
Five years ago no one
even took them seriously.
He should be killed here and now!
Priest Nick, quiet, please.
They've come a long way.
Next, let us hear the proposition
from the Recon Corps.
Yes, sir.
I am Colonel Erwin Smith, head of the Thirteenth Battalion
of the Recon Corps. Our proposition is as follows:
We will accept Eren as a formal
member of the Recon Corps,
and recapture Wall Maria
by using his Titan power.
That is all.
Is that it?
Yes. Using his abilities,
we can retake Wall Maria.
I believe the priorities are clearly apparent.
I see.
By the way, from where do you
intend to launch that operation?
Pixis, I believe the gate at
Trost was sealed for good.
Yeah. It'll probably never be opened again.
We would like to start
from Calanes in the east.
Trost
Calanes
Shiganshina
We will approach Shiganshina on a new route.
Wait! Shouldn't we seal all the gates now?
The Colossal Titan can only destroy the gates!
If we fortify those areas, they
won't be able to attack us again!
Shut up, you puppet of the traders' guild!
Using that Titan strength, we can
return to Wall Maria once again!
We're fed up with you
playing hero all the time!
You talk a lot, pig.
Who says the Titans will wait until
you can lock up all the gates?
When you say "we", are you referring to your
little friends who you plan to get fat with?
Can't you even see that people are starving
because we don't have enough land?
We're only suggesting that if we
sealed the gates, we'd be saf...
Enough of your insolence!
How dare you even suggest doing such
a thing to the sacred Wall Rose,
given unto us by God?!
You look upon the greatness of the Walls,
which transcends human understanding,
and you still can't see?!
It was their fault that it took so long
to fortify the defenses of the Walls...
They have the money and the power.
You speak blasphemy!
This is no place for a priest to speak!
What?!
Silence.
Argue about your individual beliefs
and opinions somewhere else.
Jaeger, let me ask you this:
Can you keep fighting for the
sake of mankind as a soldier,
and also use your Titan
power for the same goal?
Yes! I can.
Oh?
But in the report from Trost it says:
"He swung his fist at Mikasa Ackerman
right after becoming a Titan."
He doesn't remember that he lost control?
You want me to lie in a report?
Mankind gains nothing from hiding such a fact.
Is Mikasa Ackerman here?
Yes. I am.
You, huh?
Is it true that after he
transformed, Jaeger attacked you?
You must tell the truth. For Eren's sake.
Yes, it is true.
Titans are Titans after all!
I tried to kill Mikasa?!
I did?
But before that, he also saved my
life twice while in Titan form.
The first time,
when I was about to fall prey to a Titan,
he fought them off and defended me.
The second time,
he protected me and Armin from cannon fire.
I entreat you to consider these facts as well.
Wait a moment.
I believe this testimony is too
emotionally-biased to be accepted in court.
Mikasa Ackerman lost her parents at a young
age, and she was taken in by Jaeger's family.
However, we uncovered some surprising
details regarding those events.
Eren Jaeger and Mikasa Ackerman
were nine years old at the time.
They murdered all three robber-kidnappers.
You might call this justifiable self-defense,
but I can't help but feel disturbed by the
fundamental lack of humanity in their actions.
Can we really trust him with the fate,
funds, and manpower of mankind?
Yeah! He's probably a Titan who
infiltrated us disguised as a child!
Her too!
How can we be sure she's human?
That's right! We should
dissect her just in case!
Wait! Maybe I am a monster, but
she has nothing to do with that!
Nothing at all!
As if we could believe you!
It's a fact!
You're defending her? She must be one of you!
No!
You're wrong.
You keep using mere speculation just
to make the water flow your way.
W-What?!
First off, you've never even seen a Titan!
This isn't good.
So why are you so afraid?
I should shut up.
No, I'm gonna say it all.
I'll tell them what I think!
If those with strength don't fight, who will?
If you're too scared to fight for your
lives, then at least don't hinder me!
You cowards.
What?!
Just shut up and let me shoulder it all!
Ready!
Wait, Mikasa!
It's just my personal opinion,
but pain is the best tool for discipline.
You don't need to be educated by words.
You need training.
You've fallen low enough that
you're easy to kick around, anyway.
Hold on, Levi...
What?
It's dangerous.
What if he starts raging
and turns into a Titan?
What are you talking about?
I thought you were going to dissect him.
As I heard it, when he
turned into a Titan, he
killed 20 other Titans
before his strength ran out.
If he were an enemy, he might cause
more trouble than that intel's worth.
He still can't stand against me though.
What about you on the other hand?
All of you who persecute him, think it over.
Can you really kill him?
Supreme Commander, I have a proposal.
What is it?
Eren's Titan power has a multitude of
uncertainties and unknown elements.
It is exceedingly dangerous.
So why don't we put Eren
under Captain Levi's command
and send them on a mission outside the Walls?
Eren as well?
Yes.
Whether Eren can control his Titan power,
and whether he may be of benefit to mankind,
should be decided based on
the results of that mission.
Watch over Eren Jaeger...
Can you do that, Levi?
I can definitely kill him.
The problem is it'll either be all or nothing.
I've made my decision.
That was so mean of him. It must hurt a lot.
A little.
Where's the pain?
Sorry about doing that. But as a
result, we got you for ourselves.
Yes.
We were able to play our trump cards
at the most effective moments.
Your pain was worth our gain.
Thank you.
I look forward to working with you, Eren.
Likewise, sir!
Say, Eren.
Yes?
Do you hate me?
No. I understand it was necessary.
Glad to hear.
You could've at least held back a little.
You even broke his tooth.
Look.
Don't pick that up. It's disgusting.
It's an important sample for me.
Eren, I bet you're glad you won't be
dissected by freaks like her, huh?
Don't put me in the same league as them.
I wouldn't kill Eren.
Hey, may I see the inside of your mouth?
His tooth... already grew back.
Tatoeba ore ga oreja naitoshite
If we suppose that I am not me,
omae wa omaedato iikirerunoka
Can you say with certainty that you are you?
Suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Will you be able to pick up after yourself
- kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareruka
- Once your
sand-like shell breaks
and your heart crumbles?
Dareka no yobu koe ga
I could hear someone calling
miminari ni kawatta
But now my ears are just ringing
toki ga tomatta mitaida
It's as if time has frozen
saa me wo samase
Now, wake up
fukai yami wo ore wa arukidashita
I began to walk through a deep dark abyss
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
As swift as a gale, I escaped for my life
ikita shikabane mitaidatta
I felt like a living corpse
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
We break out of our walls
mata aouze chizu ni nai bashode
To reunite in worlds we've yet to map
Eren finally gets assigned to
the Recon Corps he so admired.
He discovers it to be a group
of people who demand change,
as well as a haven for freaks and weirdos.
That is the Recon Corps.
The Special Ops Squad
Prelude to the Counterattack (pt 2)